Contact

ladonna.christy@hotmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/ladonnachristy-phdc-rn-bc-ccrnchse-7956a223 (LinkedIn) www.harrishealth.org (Company)

Top Skills

Nursing Healthcare Management Inpatient

Certifications

Certified Healthcare Simulation Educator (CHSE)

Acute/Critical Care Knowledge Professional (Adult) (CCRN-K)

Nursing Professional Development Specialist

Ladonna Christy PhDc RN-BC CCRN CHSE

Director Of Clinical Education at CHI St. Luke's Health - Baylor St. Luke's Medical Center

Houston, Texas Area

Summary

Experienced Clinical Professor with a demonstrated history of working in the education management industry. Skilled in nursing management, critical care nursing ducation with a focus on advanced heart failure critical care supportive devices. Manage and coordinating day to day activities for a 14 bed simulation center, Medical-Surgical, JCAHO, and DNV. Strong education professional working on a Doctor of Philosophy (PhD) focused in Nursing Science from The University of Texas Health Science Center at Houston (UTHealth).

Experience

CHI St. Luke's Health - Baylor St. Luke's Medical Center Director Of Clinical Education November 2019 - Present (7 months) Houston, Texas

WGU Texas
Simulation Instructor
January 2018 - Present (2 years 5 months)

University of St. Thomas-Houston Adjunct Clinical Faculty June 2013 - Present (7 years) Houston, Texas

Houston Methodist 4 years 5 months

Nursing Program Leader, Critical Care, Houston Methodist October 2016 - November 2019 (3 years 2 months)

6565 Fannin

Nurse Education Specialist II, Critical Care July 2015 - November 2019 (4 years 5 months)

Texas Medical Center, Houston TX

Chamberlain University
Visiting Professor
October 2014 - August 2017 (2 years 11 months)

Harris Health System 4 years 2 months

Critical Care Nurse Clinical Educator February 2012 - July 2015 (3 years 6 months) Houston, Texas

Clinical Nurse Manager June 2011 - February 2013 (1 year 9 months)

Memorial Hermann Healthcare System Staff Registered Nurse January 2007 - June 2012 (5 years 6 months) Texas Medical Center/ The Woodlands

Surgical ICU/ CVICU

Education

The University of Texas Health Science Center at Houston (UTHealth)

Doctor of Philosophy (PhD), Nursing Science · (2016 - 2019)

Walden University

MSN, Ed., Educational Leadership and Administration, General · (2010 - 2013)

The University of Texas at El Paso BSN, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse